<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
	<title>picklenerd - tutorials</title>
	<link href="https://picklenerd.github.io/blog/tags/tutorials/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
	<link href="https://picklenerd.github.io/blog"/>
	<generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
	<updated>2019-06-02T09:44:00-04:00</updated>
	<id>https://picklenerd.github.io/blog/tags/tutorials/atom.xml</id>
	<entry xml:lang="en">
		<title>PNGme: An Intermediate Rust Project</title>
		<published>2019-06-02T09:44:00-04:00</published>
		<updated>2019-06-02T09:44:00-04:00</updated>
		<link href="https://picklenerd.github.io/blog/pngme-book/" type="text/html"/>
		<id>https://picklenerd.github.io/blog/pngme-book/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hello there! Long time no blog.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#x27;s been 3 years since I wrote a few blog posts about my experience learning Rust. Since then, I&#x27;ve been using Rust for just about every project I have outside of work. It even weaseled its way into a few of my dev tools at work, and now we even have a new service that&#x27;s written in Rust. You might say that I&#x27;m a fan.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#x27;ve been meaning to write some learning material for a long time. There are plenty of resources for beginners, but there&#x27;s isn&#x27;t much out there for people who are know the basics but aren&#x27;t quite ready to jump into their own projects. I&#x27;m the kind of person that will just bash my head against a problem until I figure it out, but a lot of people aren&#x27;t and there aren&#x27;t a ton of resources out there for those people. The &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;blog.rust-lang.org&#x2F;2020&#x2F;04&#x2F;17&#x2F;Rust-survey-2019.html&quot;&gt;2019 survey&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; came to the same conclusion.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year my coworker found a blog post about hiding messages in PNG files. I made it about sentence in before I closed it and ran off to figure it out myself. I wrote a little command line tool in Rust and he wrote a script in Kotlin, and then we had some fun on Slack. It&#x27;s always been one of my favorite Rust repos because it&#x27;s small and mostly self-contained. It was also a lot of fun to write and a lot of fun to play with after it was done. I decided it would be perfect for an intermediate tutorial.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;picklenerd.github.io&#x2F;pngme_book&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Check it out&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; if you&#x27;re sitting in that intermediate space and wondering what to do next.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
